<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on 0xhead</title>
    <link>https://oxhead.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on 0xhead</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016 Chin-Jung Hsu</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/project/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Pisces: A P2P Meta-Grid System</title>
      <link>https://oxhead.github.io/project/pisces-a-p2p-meta-grid-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oxhead.github.io/project/pisces-a-p2p-meta-grid-system/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To support various Grid services to satisfy with heterogeneous needs, the Grids integrated with distinct types of services provided by spreading resources across the network. This project will develop the hierarchical architecture to coordinate spreading Grid resources. For the purposed of developing distributed autonomic Grid systems, the centralized coordination architecture is utilized to manage the intra-Grid resources and the Peer-to-Peer (P2P) technology is applied to communicate with inter-Grid systems. The Pisces project will exploit Grid system management and P2P technology to construct P2P computing Grid system and P2P data Grid system with the consideration of integrating with two types of Grid resources: computing resources and storage resources. The Grid system information could be integrated by developing the information monitoring system. With exploiting the computing resource management system and the data storage management system, resource accessing in Grid system could be super intended. Moreover, rely on metadata catalog management system and P2P middleware to communicate with distributed autonomic Grid systems and to support the developing mechanism for resource discovery and metadata catalog lookup. Based on the aforementioned techniques, this project will be applied P2P technology to Grid system to construct a P2P Meta-Grid system. The Pisces project could not only achieve cross-Grid systems and improve the scalability, but also provide a platform for large-scale application development and testing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;pisces_architecture.png&#34; alt=&#34;Pisces Architecture&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
